<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalKotlinProject</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="user" />
    <string name="cart" />
    <string name="search" />
    <string name="home" />
    <string name="position_tag" />
    <string name="total_price">Total Price: %d</string>
    <string name="yslDesc">La Nuit de L\'Homme Bleu Électrique was created by Dominique Ropion and IFF. Top notes are Cardamom, Ginger and Bergamot; middle notes are Lavender and Geranium; base notes are Cedar and Vetiver.</string>
    <string name="missdior">The nose behind this fragrance is Francois Demachy. Top notes are Iris, Peony and Lily-of-the-Valley; middle notes are Apricot, Rose and Peach; base notes are Vanilla, Musk, Tonka Bean, Benzoin and Sandalwood.</string>
    <string name="DiorSauvage">The nose behind this fragrance is Francois Demachy. Top notes are Calabrian bergamot and Pepper; middle notes are Sichuan Pepper, Lavender, Pink Pepper, Patchouli, Geranium and elemi; base notes are Ambroxan, Cedar and Labdanum.</string>
    <string name="Flowerbomb">The nose behind this fragrance is Domitille Michalon Bertier. Top notes are Peach and Vine; middle note is Orchid; base note is Vanilla Bean.</string>
    <string name="DiGioProfumo">The nose behind this fragrance is Alberto Morillas. Top notes are Sea Notes and Bergamot; middle notes are Rosemary, Sage and Geranium; base notes are Incense and Patchouli.</string>
    <string name="ErosFemme">Eros Pour Femme was created by Alberto Morillas, Olivier Cresp and Nathalie Lorson. Top notes are Sicilian Lemon, Pomegranate and Bergamot; middle notes are Lemon Blossom and Peony; base notes are Musk, Ambroxan, Woodsy Notes and Sandalwood.</string>
    <string name="ErosFlame">The nose behind this fragrance is Aurelien Guichard. Top notes are Mint, Green Apple and Lemon; middle notes are Tonka Bean, Ambroxan and Geranium; base notes are Madagascar Vanilla, Virginian Cedar, Atlas Cedar, Vetiver and Oakmoss.</string>
    <string name="YSLLibre">Libre Eau de Toilette was created by Anne Flipo and Carlos Benaim. Top notes are Lavender, Bergamot and Mandarin Orange; middle notes are Orange Blossom, Jasmine Tea and Jasmine; base notes are Musk, Vanilla and Ambergris.</string>
    <string name="YSLBleuElec">La Nuit de L\'Homme Bleu Électrique was created by Dominique Ropion and IFF. Top notes are Cardamom, Ginger and Bergamot; middle notes are Lavender and Geranium; base notes are Cedar and Vetiver.</string>
    <string name="profileDescription">As a member you can get exclusive deals and notifications of new products or offers. If you wish to unsubscribe from our newsletter, remove your account</string>
</resources>